The footage you are about to watch is of a sensitive nature
and although it may not be suitable for all viewers, it is for the glory of God.
Lord I believe
Help me overcome my unbelief
She is free!
Put your hands together for the King of Glory!
MIRACLE HEALING Caught On Tape!
Before and After
Who is like my Jesus
In this world
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 01/04/2019